I would like to go to the shrine as soon as possible.
I've always wanted one.
I've been wanting to get it for a long time.
The hard part
I did it!
Hello, this is Miyazu Sumide.
I've arrived in Kyoto
It was in Kyoto that I got on the Shinkansen
I was also on the drowned divers when I came to the prefecture
When we came back, Konaka went into the field
7.8 short cower
I'm going to go for a bit
Yes, I'm here at Nanzenji Temple.
It's very relaxing.
It's still difficult.
I'm embarrassed.
It's a little bit difficult to be alone and chatty.
It's only my first day.
I'll get used to it little by little.
This is my growth journal.
I'll do my best
Ranjenji, let's go.
You put it in there, didn't you?
It's okay.
I've always wanted to do this.
I could do the Sacred Heart all by myself.
This is the famous bridge.
It's a beautiful structure.
It's amazing.
We're here at the Kyoto Art Museum.
I'm on my way.
Okay, now we're going to see the Bankside exhibit, which I really wanted to see.
We're up on the roof. Wow.
It's so beautiful. It really is.
I'm so excited.
Look at this. This is what I wanted to see.
It's a beautiful building.
It's amazing.
Hey, Mom.
It's so cute!
Wow!
The wind feels good.
It's gonna look good on this.
It's big.
Much wider.
This is the rooftop.
Nature and
and architecture
fusion of nature and architecture
It's like a fusion of nature and architecture.
If there was a hole
I want to go in.
Yes, sir.
I'll show you.
The first day in Kyoto is over.
I'm looking at Kyoto station.
I'm looking at the view of Kyoto station.
And the tower.
I'm going to go back to the hotel now.
I'm going back to the hotel now.
I'm so hungry and happy!
Yes, it's evening now.
Today I wanted to see something that I really wanted to see.
And to get a good luck charm of congratulations!
Here we are!
Ta-da!
Shimogamo Shrine!
I'd like to go and pay my respects right away!
Here we go!
Oh, wow!
It's big, wow!
By my own eto...
What is this?
It seems that each person goes to the shrine in a different direction
It seems that each direction of worship is different.
I'm a bird, so...
So this way.
A plaster duck.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to eat this duck with my hand.
Birds and chickens and hens
A little bit lined up there.
I've never done anything like this before.
I'm very much looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
So I went to the shrine.
Since it was the Year of the Bird, I visited the shrine early.
The Year of the Dragon is very popular this year.
I got in line because it was the year of the dragon, too.
It was very crowded!
And you know what?
There is a reason why I wanted to come to Shimogamo Shrine.
That's because...
I've always wanted a good luck charm from this shrine
I wanted to get it!
The reason why I wanted to get this good luck charm so badly is...
I heard it's very cute!
I hope they have it.
Amulet
Here we are!
Here it is!
It's just like this!
Carefully stitched one by one.
It's so cute and delicate
I just had to see it.
I had to have it!
I came all the way here!
It's so cute!
It's one of my own.
It's great.
This one's cute, too.
This one's pretty, too.
I got this one.
Cute.
I'm going to play the lake lottery now.
If you do this for a while, it seems to make letters come to life.
I'm doing it.
I'm so excited.
I'm so relieved.
It's coming up... great, great, great, great...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait.
I did it!
That's great!
I'm so happy!
I did it!
I can do whatever I want.
If you're not careful
it won't work
Let's not let our guard down.
You can't be too sure at first.
You're right. You're right. You're right.
It is important
To protect the realistic use of momentum
I'll keep it.
Now it's time to work
I'm going to put myself in the right place and work hard
I can see it now
I got it.
How'd it go?
Trip.
Oh, it was great.
That's great!
It's already today's big day.
I'm so happy this year!
Good morning!
Good morning
Today is the morning of the third and final day in Kyoto
First thing on the third day, we came to Arashiyama, a beautiful mountain.
Yes, this is Tenryuji Temple, which is a World Heritage Site.
The curry sausage is beautiful.
It's true!
I've always wanted to see it.
I've never seen it before.
Frog, frog, frog, frog.
It's like he's on my shoulder.
That's my mom.
It's beautiful.
Good night.
Refreshing.
Oh, I ate.
Good morning
I'm here for the moon
Glad to see you! The weather is soooo nice!
Conan's place
Yes!
I've been wanting to come here for a long time.
I'd like to go across now.
Thank you for watching!
Yes, so my New Year's Day
Today and I was on a 2 day trip!
It was a bit of a loose end.
I hope you enjoyed it!
Thank you, bye bye thank you.
Thank you very much!
This is Sumire Miyaji.
Thank you for watching.